<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>html on fustilio personal webpage</title>
    <link>/tags/html/</link>
    <description>Recent content in html on fustilio personal webpage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="/tags/html/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Enhanced Spatial Awareness for the Visually Impaired using Mixed Reality and Vibrotactile Feedback</title>
      <link>/2020/02/mixed-reality-vision/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 19:26:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2020/02/mixed-reality-vision/</guid>
      <description>One in six people have some form of visual impairment ranging from mild vision loss to total blindness. The visually impaired constantly face the danger of walking into people or hazardous objects. This project proposes the use of vibrotactile feedback to serve as an obstacle detection system for visually impaired users. We utilize a mixed reality headset with on-board depth sensors to build a digital map of the real world and a suit with an array of actuators to provide feedback as to indicate to the visually impaired the position of obstacles around them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DoodleCloud: Drawing in the Sky</title>
      <link>/2020/02/doodle-cloud/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 11:00:05 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2020/02/doodle-cloud/</guid>
      <description>DoodleCloud was made as part of the Global VR Hackathon 2019 which I participated with Caryn. We were given 48-hours and the theme of the hackathon was &amp;lsquo;Cloud&amp;rsquo;. We developed a VR drawing game, DoodleCloud, where players would try their best to draw pictures in the sky using their finger.
From past experiences, we knew the importance of having a winning idea before anything. We began our ideation process by penning down words related to &amp;lsquo;Cloud&amp;rsquo; and studying the capabilities of the VR Headsets that were provided.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hacking the Hack</title>
      <link>/2020/02/hackathon-methodology/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 11:00:05 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2020/02/hackathon-methodology/</guid>
      <description>DoodleCloud DoodleCloud was made as part of the Global VR Hackathon 2019 which I participated with Caryn. We were given 48-hours and the theme of the hackathon was &amp;ldquo;Cloud&amp;rdquo;. We developed a VR drawing game, DoodleCloud, where players would try their best to draw pictures in the sky using their finger.
From past experiences, we knew the importance of having a winning idea before anything. We began our ideation process by penning down words related to &amp;ldquo;Cloud&amp;rdquo; and studying the capabilities of the VR Headsets that were provided.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ConnectCane: Navigation Aid for the Visually Impaired</title>
      <link>/2020/02/connect-cane/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 23:00:05 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2020/02/connect-cane/</guid>
      <description>Using NFC tags embedded in tactile paving and an NFC reader attached to a white cane to give the visually impaired more information. Background Without assistance, visually impaired individuals might often find themselves in dangerous situations due to their lack of spatial awareness or understanding of their environment. For example, road crossings or approaching escalators in the opposite direction. At these danger areas, tactile paving would allow the visually impaired to be alerted but what if the tactile paving would tell them more?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ml Agents Examples</title>
      <link>/2020/01/ml-agents-examples/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 11:40:19 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2020/01/ml-agents-examples/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m a little blown away by some of these ML-Agents demos I&amp;rsquo;ve seen on YouTube.
ML-Agents Showcase Explorer Drone - Github link</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello There I&amp;rsquo;ve just recently graduated from the National University of Singapore with a Bachelor of Engineering (Computer Engineering) specializing in Interactive Digital Media and am currently working on a variety of small projects while looking for a job that fits!
I&amp;rsquo;d like to think that studying Computer Engineering has given me a wide range of skillsin both hardware and software domains and I&amp;rsquo;m currently interested in developing applications for virtual/augmented reality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Template Post</title>
      <link>/2020/01/template-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 15:13:33 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2020/01/template-post/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>So I made this 3D pong game you can&#39;t even play</title>
      <link>/2020/01/pong-3d-ml/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2020 23:22:20 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2020/01/pong-3d-ml/</guid>
      <description>In a previous hackathon I participated in, there was a project that prototyped the use of machine learning to &amp;ldquo;evolve&amp;rdquo; the capability of in-game AI agents by using user provided input through a Virtual Reality game. I was pretty blown away by the idea of evolution through repetitive training and exposure to user-provided input. I&amp;rsquo;ve seen a couple of videos where developers created simulations with Unity and thought that it might be cool to give it a try myself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Initial Commit</title>
      <link>/2020/01/initial-commit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2020 20:48:19 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2020/01/initial-commit/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Finally got down to creating this site, without any customization and the entirety of the site is pretty much identical to the example site provided. I just wanted some place to pen down my ideas and projects before I forget and in true maker spirit I hope to be able to share some of the lessons I&amp;rsquo;ve learnt along the way.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Markdown Syntax Guide</title>
      <link>/2019/03/markdown-syntax/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/03/markdown-syntax/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Hugo content files, also it shows whether basic HTML elements are decorated with CSS in a Hugo theme.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rich Content</title>
      <link>/2019/03/rich-content/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/03/rich-content/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hugo ships with several &lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io/content-management/shortcodes/#use-hugo-s-built-in-shortcodes&#34;&gt;Built-in Shortcodes&lt;/a&gt; for rich content, along with a &lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io/about/hugo-and-gdpr/&#34;&gt;Privacy Config&lt;/a&gt; and a set of Simple Shortcodes that enable static and no-JS versions of various social media embeds.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Placeholder Text</title>
      <link>/2019/03/placeholder-text/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/03/placeholder-text/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Lorem est tota propiore conpellat pectoribus de
pectora summo.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emoji Support</title>
      <link>/2019/03/emoji-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/03/emoji-support/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Emoji can be enabled in a Hugo project in a number of ways.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
